I'm not gonna get my pecan pie,
am I?
(Leonard:)You want some Oreos?
- Double Stuf?
- No, it's regular.
(Sheldon:)Nice. Kick a man when he's down.
(Sheldon:)I'm glad we're finally getting to do
something together, just the two of us.
(Mrs Cooper:)Sure. One thing you really miss
when you're on vacation is laundry.
(Sheldon:)Careful,
you're using too much Downy.
(Sheldon:)You know if my clothes
get too soft it makes me sleepy.
(Mrs Cooper:)Well, this takes me back. Me doing
your laundry, you next to me criticizing.
(Sheldon:)It is nice, isn't it?
(Leonard:)Mrs. Cooper.
(Mrs Cooper:)- Hi.
- Oh, hello, darling.
(Penny:)Sheldon, you didn't tell me
your mom was coming.
(Sheldon:)It was in my weekly e-mail blast.
(Sheldon:)Right between
"Beet season is finally here"...
...and "Uh-oh, red stool from beets
Ieads to cancer scare."
- So how have you been?
- Good, good.
Leonard has a new girIfriend.
How are you doing with all that?